

Elmehdi AGUENDICH

Software Engineer

Salé, Morocco +212 631 232 736

mehdi_aguendich@protonmail.com

in LinkedIn | GitHub | 5 Portfolio

SUMMARY

Junior Software Engineer with one year of professional experience in the development of software solutions, including one dedicated to internal documents and customer relationship management. Proficient in Java, TypeScript and REST API. Machine Learning and Computer Vision enthusiast.

EXPERIENCE _

URBAN AGENCY DAKHLA-OUED EDDAHAB

Dec. 2022 - Present / Dakhla-Oued Eddahab, Morocco ·

IT ENGINEER, FULL-TIME

- Development and Maintenance of solutions dedicated to the management of the Agency's many data fluxes .
- Maintenance of hardware solutions and of the electronic park (Servers, PCs, Printers ...)
- Correcting Hardware/Software errors.
- Windows administration of the different employees accounts.

INOVAR *Apr 2022 - Sep 2022 · 5 mos / Remote*

PEGA System Architect, Full-time remote

- PEGA System Architect certification course.
- Software solution evolution and maintenance using PEGA System tools.

TECHNOLOGY STACK:

• PEGA Appstudio | PEGA Devstudio

ASATECHNO CONSULTING

Dec 2021 - Feb 2022 · 3 mos / Kénitra, Morocco

SOFTWARE ENGINEER, INTERNSHIP

- · Work environment preparation.
- Collaborative teamwork using a CI/CD tool.
- Insurance sector software solutions evolution and maintenance.
- Documentation of all tasks mentioned above.

TECHNOLOGY STACK:

CI/CD | Java | Play | React | Scala | Scala.js

Tools:

• Eclipse | GitLab CI/CD | Intelli| IDEA | SBT

ISO OUAL TECH.

Mar 2021 - Sep 2021 · 6 mos / Salé, Morocco

SOFTWARE ENGINEER, INTERNSHIP

• Enterprise internal commercial flow management, software solution design and implementation.

TECHNOLOGY STACK:

Angular 11 | exceljs | PDF.js | REST | Spring (Boot, Data, Security) | UML

Tools:

• Eclipse | Microsoft Excel | MongoDB | MySQL | VS Code

EDUCATION

ÉCOLE MAROCAINE DES SCIENCES DE L'INGÉNIEUR

2017-2021 / Rabat, Morocco

STATE ENGINEER DEGREE, COMPUTER SCIENCE AND NETWORKS OPTION: MIAGE

INSTITUT D'AGRICULTURE ET VETERINARIAT HASSAN II

2014-2017 / Rabat, Morocco

CORE CURRICULUM OPTION: AGRONOMY

BACCALAUREAT DEGREE, OPTION: MATHEMATICAL SCIENCES -A-

SKILLS _

SOFTWARE DEVELOPMENT *Proficient:* Angular 12 | Java | Python | Spring (Boot, Security) | TypeScript

Familiar: GitLab | MongoDB | MySQL | Next.js | Node.js | Spring (Data) | UML

LANGUES *Native:* Arabic *Professionnel:* French | English | German

INTERESTS _

• Reading: Crime and Punishment (Fyodor Dostoevsky) | Le Monde de Sophie (Jostein Gaarder).

- Excursion : Excursion to the summit of "La Cathédrale".
- Music : Music theory and 5th year guitar diploma. Conservatoire Dar El Baroud, Salé.